# Hadi Lashkari-Ghouchani

### Senior Android Developer

@ hadilashkari@gmail.com

+98 939 125 8116

Tehran Iran

github.com/hadilq

🖹 stackoverflow.com/users/2482947 in linkedin.com/in/hadi-lashkari-ghouchani-97864934

#### SUMMARY

Professional guy with 3+ years of experience in Android development who has profound learning, contributing and R&D skills. Creative person who prefers to not inventing the wheel, but in case of performance, memory management, app size and security can and will invent a spherical wheel. A result oriented and passionate developer who enjoys solving problems and creating new features.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Android Developer / Functional Manager

at Sheypoor

🛗 Jan. 2018 - Present

O Tehran, Iran

Sheypoor is one of lead classifieds marketplaces in Iran with over 1.5M users per day.

#### Missions:

- As the functional manager of Android team, I'm responsible for the code quality of Sheypoor app. I coach the team to practice design patterns, clean code and using app architecture, along with updating libraries and adding new features with focus on agility and UX.
- Beside other features, I like a feature that downloads static data, which includes locations and categories, in the build time and inserting them into a database then using that database as an asset in run
- · Redesign the entire app, including rebranding, for summer campaign

#### Technologies:

- Dagger 2, RxJava 2, Butter Knife, Greendao, etc.
- · Agile, Kanban, Git Flow, CI/CD
- Mockito, Espresso, Jacoco
- Pivotal Tracker, Github, Jenkins, Slack, Zeplin, etc.

## Senior Android Developer

at Myket

🛗 Sep. 2015 - Des. 2017

Tehran, Iran

Myket is one of lead app stores in Iran with over 8+ million users.

- Starting TDD and installing Jenking's pipeline to handle CI/CD.
- Implementing features such as handling deeplinks, search page, inbox page, etc.

- Volley, One Signal, EventBus, OrmLite, etc.
- · Agile, Scrum, Git Flow
- · Mockito, Espresso
- · Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Gitlab, Jfrog, Jenkins

## Java and C# developer

mar. 2015 - Aug. 2015

O Tehran, Iran

SOHA was formed to focus on solutions based on smart cards

#### Missions:

- Download a jpeg image from a RFID card and show it in an Android app by using bluetooth connection.
- · Impelementing Android and desktop apps.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sharif University Of Technolog Feb. 2010 M.Sc in Physics Payame-Noor University of Mashad B.Sc in Physics Jul. 2007

#### TOOLS / SKILLS

## Android library

Dagger 2/RxJava 2/Retrofit 2 Butter Knife/JetPack/

# Android test library

JUnit/Mockito/Espresso/Jacoco/...

### Tool

Gradle/Maven/Ant/Make/Git/Subversion/...

### Command Line Tool

grep/sed/netstat/awk/docker/... adb/sdkmanager/avdmanager/...

## Development Tool

Pivotal Tracker/Jira/Jenkins/...

## Programing Language

Java/Kotlin/Scala/Python Groovy/Dart/Javascript/Rust/...

## Operating System

Linux(Fedora/Ubuntu)

#### LANGUAGE

English: Advance Farsi: Native

The source of this resume in github

Built this resume in September 7, 2018